Guide to the Western Connecticut State University Photographs and Miscellanea RG 8
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series I: Photographs, 45605
  - Events, 46240
    - Miscellaneous, 46370
      - Million Mom March; Individuals and groups (unlabeled) Includes Pres.Roach and P.Ivry, 2000; 50198 (Box 6.2, Folder 3)
      - Musical Performance; Garah and Gregory Landes of Synchronicity w/Irving Medina, organ student and David Smith, 2001; 50199 (Box 6.2, Folder 4)
      - Open House; Westside, Candids (unlabeled), 2000; 50200 (Box 6.2, Folder 5)
      - Patriotic Sing (Sept. 25, 2001), 50322 (Box 10.3, Folder 30)
      - Pick a Major Fair; Midtown, Candids (unlabeled), 2000; 50201 (Box 6.2, Folder 6)
      - PTA Conference; Group (unlabeled), 2001; 50202 (Box 6.2, Folder 7)
      - Public Private Partnership; Group (unlabeled), 2001; 50203 (Box 6.2, Folder 8)
        One 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Red Cross; Group, Posed, Includes Blood Drive (unlabeled), 2000; 50204 (Box 6.2, Folder 9)
      - Research Ethics; Candids (Alysia Maffucci, Research Compliance Officer, Univ.of Connecticut Storrs), 2002; 50205 (Box 6.2, Folder 10)
        Four 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Quad Day 2000, 50327 (Box 10.3, Folder 33)
      - Residence Halls "Moving In Day", 1998; 50328 (Box 10.3, Folder 34)
      - Science Horizons; Posed and candids (unlabeled), 2000; 50206 (Box 6.2, Folder 11)
      - Social Service Workshop; Candids (unlabeled), 1998; 50207 (Box 6.2, Folder 12)
      - Support Center for Non-Profit Management; Groups, Candids (unlabeled), 2002; 50208 (Box 6.2, Folder 14)
        Three 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Tedesco Awards Night; Posed, groups (unlabeled), 1998; 50209 (Box 6.2, Folder 15)
      - Joe Torre event; Group, posed (unlabeled), 1987; 50210 (Box 6.2, Folder 16)
        One 4x6 color; not an image of Joe Torre.
      - Toys for Tots; Candids (Includes Pres. Roach and Walter Bernstein), 2000-2001; 50211 (Box 6.2, Folder 17)
        Ten 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Unknown Event; Patti Ivry (speaker), ca.2000; 50212 (Box 6.2, Folder 18)
        Two 3.5x5 color
      - Unknown Event; Group (includes Patti Ivry), 2001; 50213 (Box 6.2, Folder 19)
      - WCSU Bond Commission; Candids (Gov.Rowland,Pres.Roach,R.Sullivan), 2002; 50214 (Box 6.2, Folder 25)
        Eight 4x6 color w/negatives
      - WCSU Foundation; Rick Arconti appointed Foundation Chair w/Dr.J.Roach, 2000; 50215 (Box 6.2, Folder 26)
      - WCSU Foundation Board; Groups, Posed (unlabeled), 1998-2000; 50216 (Box 6.2, Folder 27)
        Six 4x6 color WCSU@Waterbury WCSU@Waterbury
      - WCSU@Waterbury; Posed and Candids (unlabeled), ca 2000; 50217 (Box 6.2, Folder 33)
      - Western Weekly; Posed and candids (Includes H.Masterson,Chancellor Cibes, H.Janick,J.Pegolotti,J.Briggs, J.Sikora,J.Briggs,C.Kukk,J.Roach,H.Tritter,S.Neuwirth, and several unlabeled), 1998-2002; 50218 (Box 6.2, Folder 34)
        11 4x6 color w/negatives
      - WestFest, 1998; 50330 (Box 10.4, Folder 17)
        Nine 3.5x5 b/w
      - Miscellaneous A-Z; Additional images for boxes 5.3-5.4; 6.2-6.3; 10.2, 10.3, 10.4; 22.1-22.2, ca.1990-2000; 50320 (Box 31)
        Approximately 500 images
      - Miscellaneous COM-HE; Additional images for boxes 5.3-5-4; 6.2-6.3; 10.2, 10.3, 10.4; 22.1-22.2, ca.1990-2000; 50332 (Box 32)
      - Miscellaneous HI-Staff; Additional images for boxes 5.3-5.4; 6.2-6.3; 10.2, 10.3, 10.4; 22.1-22.2, ca.1990-2000; 50333 (Box 34)
      - Miscellaneous Staff-Y; Additional images for boxes 5.3-5.4; 6.2-6.3; 10.2,10.3,10.4; 22.1-22.2, ca.1990-2000; 50334 (Box 34)
    - University Annual Ball, 46334
      - Dr. James Roach/Dr. Denise Hogan, Nathan Ancell, Gene Eriquez, 1998-2003, 1998-1999; 46369 (Box 7, Folder 1)
        Three 4x6 and one 5x7color
      - Theme: Mississippi Showboat; Special Guests: Mark & Livy Twain, 2000; 46368 (Box 7, Folder 2)
        Nine 5x5 and seven 4x6 color
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 1), 2001; 46367 (Box 7, Folder 3)
        17 - 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 1), 2001; 46366 (Box 7, Folder 4)
        11 roll assignments
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 2), 2001; 46365 (Box 7, Folder 5)
        15 - 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 2), 2001; 46364 (Box 7, Folder 6)
        8 roll assignments
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 3), 2001; 46363 (Box 7, Folder 7)
        16 - 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 3), 2001; 46362 (Box 7, Folder 8)
        14 roll assignments
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 4), 2001; 46361 (Box 7, Folder 9)
        21 - 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 4), 2001; 46360 (Box 7, Folder 10)
        10 roll assignments
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 5), 2001; 46359 (Box 7, Folder 11)
        13 - 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 5), 2001; 46358 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 6), 2001; 46357 (Box 7, Folder 13)
        20 - 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 6), 2001; 46356 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 7), 2001; 46355 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 7), 2001; 46354 (Box 7, Folder 16)
        7 roll assignments
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 8), 2001; 46353 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 8), 2001; 46352 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 9), 2001; 46351 (Box 7, Folder 19)
        4 - 4x6 color w/negatives
      - Theme: An Evening at the Acropolis (Roll 9), 2001; 46350 (Box 7, Folder 20)
        3 roll assignments
      - Roll 1, 2002; 46349 (Box 7, Folder 21)
        Five roll assignments and contact sheet
      - Roll 2, 2002; 46348 (Box 7, Folder 22)
        Six roll assignments and contact sheet
      - Roll 3, 2002; 46347 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Roll 4, 2002; 46346 (Box 7, Folder 24)
        Three 4x6 color w/contact sheet
      - Roll 4, 2002; 46345 (Box 7, Folder 25)
        Seven roll assignments
      - Roll 5, 2002; 46344 (Box 7, Folder 26)
        Three roll assignments
      - Roll 5, 2002; 46343 (Box 7, Folder 27)
        Six 4x6 color w/contact sheet
      - Roll 6, 2002; 46342 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Roll 7, 2002; 46341 (Box 7, Folder 29)
        Five roll assignments
      - Roll 7, 2002; 46340 (Box 7, Folder 30)
        One 4x6 color and one contact sheet
      - Roll 8, 2002; 46339 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Roll 8, 2002; 46338 (Box 7, Folder 32)
        Ten 4x6 color w/contact sheet
      - Roll 9, 2002; 46337 (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Rolls 1, 2, 3, 4, 2003; 46336 (Box 7, Folder 34)
        29 roll assignments
      - Rolls 5, 6, 7, 8, 2003; 46335 (Box 7, Folder 35)
        17 roll assignments
      - Individuals/groups; Includes Stephen Feldman, Skitch Henderson, James Dyer and wives, 1986; 50018 (Box 6.1, Folder 7)
        One b/w contact sheet, 15 4x6 color, w/color negatives
      - Individuals/groups, 1987; 50019 (Box 6.1, Folder 8)
      - Individuals/groups, ca.1990; 50136 (Box 6.2, Folder 20)
        Six 3.5x5 color
      - Individuals/groups, 1997; 50137 (Box 6.2, Folder 21)
      - Individuals/groups, 1999; 50138 (Box 6.2, Folder 22)
      - Individuals/groups, 2001; 50139 (Box 6.2, Folder 23)
        Seven 4x6 color and one partial image
      - Individuals/groups, 2001; 50140 (Box 36)
        Approximately 200 4x6 color
      - Individuals/groups; (Includes Dr.Roach,Dr.Hogan, Dr.Morton, Farooq Kathwari), 2002; 50141 (Box 6.2, Folder 24)
      - Rolls A-F (additional images) unlabeled, 2002; 50142 (Box 36)
    - Visitors, 46264
      - Abernathy, Ralph A. (American civil rights leader), ca 1960-2003, 1971; 46333 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Adamson, Rebecca, President's Lecture Series "Ancient Futures", 1998; 46332 (Box 8, Folder 2)
        Nine 4x6 color (w/negatives)
      - The Airmen of Note (official jazz ensemble of the U.S. Air Force), 1972; 46331 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Ancell, Nathan (co-founder of Ethan Allen) and Lawrence Davidson, Chairman of the CSU Board of Trustees, ca.1980; 46330 (Box 8, Folder 4a)
        Two 8x10 b/w (includes negatives of Ancell w/students)
      - Ancell School/Arconti Lecture "Ethics in Business" Peter Came (Incl.Robert Berzok, Violet Manon, Jacqueline Smith, Nathan Ancell, Dimples Armstrong,, John Geddes, Jan Alexander, Paul Steinmetz, Jr., Robert S. Mellis), April 1989; 50022 (Box 6.1, Folder 10)
        14 4x6 color, 18 5x7 b/w
      - Armstrong, Kenneth (English footballer), ca.1960-1970; 46329 (Box 8, Folder 4b)
      - Beecher, John (activist poet), ca.1970; 46328 (Box 8, Folder 5)
        One 5x7 b/w; two 3.5 x 5 b/w
      - Buckley, William F. Jr. (author and conservative commentator), 1991; 46327 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Burgess, Russ (parapsychologist), 1968; 46326 (Box 8, Folder 7)
        One 8x10 and one 3.5 x 5 b/w
      - Chase, Stuart (economist and engineer), ca.1960; 46325 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Cibes, William (Chancellor CSUS), 1995; 46324 (Box 8, Folder 9)
        Two 4x6 b/w; one 4x6 and one 3.5 x 5 color
      - Collins, Billy, U.S. Poet Laureate (poetry reading), 2002; 46323 (Box 8, Folder 10)
        One 4x6 b/w
      - Copeland, Aaron (composer), 1974; 46322 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Cousy, Bob (basketball clinic), 1964; 46321 (Box 8, Folder 12)
        One 4x5 and one 4x4 b/w
      - Danish Gym Team, 1968; 46320 (Box 8, Folder 13)
        Six 8x10 and two 7x8 b/w
      - Deming, W. Edwards (statistician, author, lecturer, and consultant), 1990; 46319 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Dodd, Christopher (Connecticut politician), ca.1980; 46318 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Doors, The (rock band), 1967; 46317 (Box 8, Folder 16)
        One 3.5 x 5 b/w (with two negatives)
      - Eiseley, Dr. Loren (anthropologist, ecologist, author and poet), 1968; 46316 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Fisher, Roger, Harvard Law School, ca.1990; 46315 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Franks, Lucinda (author), 1991; 46314 (Box 8, Folder 19)
        One 5x7b/w
      - Goodall, Jane (primatologist, ethologist, anthropologist), ca.1990; 46313 (Box 8, Folder 20)
        One 4x5 bw/; two 5x7 color; and one 8x10 b/w w/historic photographs
      - Grasso, Ella T. (Governor of Connecticut) see also Gov Luncheon 1979, 1975; 46312 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Green, Raphael, 1968; 46311 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Haig, Alexander M., Jr. (Gen.U.S.Army, Secretary of State, etc.), ca.1980; 46310 (Box 8, Folder 23)
        Two 5x7 b/w (w/negatives); four b/w contact sheets
      - Harlem Globe Trotters (posed with child), 1995; 46309 (Box 8, Folder 24)
        One 3.5 x 5 duotone
      - Harzic, Jean (French Cultural Attache), 1968; 46308 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Henderson, Skitch (musician, conductor, WCSU Prof. of Music), ca.1980-2000; 46307 (Box 8, Folder 26)
        Two 8x10 b/w; one 5x7 b/w photo
      - Henneberry, Dave, 1999; 46306 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Hill, Warren G., Dir. Higher Education for Conn. (chair presentation), 1970; 46305 (Box 8, Folder 28)
        Nine 3.5 x 3.5, four 5x7 b/w (w/negatives)
      - Hyman, Sam, ca.1990; 46304 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - IBM (S.Vehslage, H.Horowitz, C.Bruce: first univ. based advanced technological classroom, 1989; 46303 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Jones, James Earl, President's Lecture Series "The Culture Quest", 2002; 46302 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Juran, Joseph M., Deming Lecture Series, 1992; 46301 (Box 8, Folder 32)
        One 5x7 color
      - Kennedy, Robert (CEO Union Carbide)(Event unknown 11/5/86)., 1986; 46300 (Box 8, Folder 33)
        Nine 5x7 b/w photos w/ contact sheets and negatives
      - Kissenger, Henry A. (author, politician, Secretary of State), ca.1980; 46299 (Box 8, Folder 34)
        Two 8x10 b/w (w/negatives)
      - Krupa, Eugene (Gene) B. (jazz and big band drummer), 1963; 46298 (Box 8, Folder 35)
        Two 9x10 and one 8/10 b/w
      - Laffer, Dr. A., Carbide Lecturer (economist, Laffer/Thurow debate), 1982; 46297 (Box 8, Folder 36)
        Two 8x10 and five 5x7 b/w (w/contact sheets and negatives)
      - Macricostas, Constantine, Marie Macricostas, Dr. Linda Vaden-Goad, 2003; 46296 (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Malino, Rabbi Jerome w/Dr. James Roach; Alumni Reunion Class of 1946, Nov. 1996, 46295 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - Manhattan String Quartet, ca.1970; 46294 (Box 8, Folder 39a)
      - Mighty, Mighty Bosstones, 1999 (Box 6.1, Folder 16.1)
        1, 8x10" black and white print; publicity photo.
      - Minford, Robert as Edgar Allan Poe, 1968; 46293 (Box 8, Folder 39b)
      - Moss, Donald (illustrator) with Ralph Holibaugh and Abe Echevarria, 1999; 46292 (Box 8, Folder 39c)
        Eight 4x6 b/w
      - Ralph Nader (political activist) w/Danbury Mayor Arconti, ca.1970; 46291 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      - Noslier, Odette (Music Academy of the West), ca.1960; 46290 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - O'Neill, William A. (Governor of Connecticut), 1980; 46289 (Box 8, Folder 42)
        One 8x10, four 5x7 b/w; two 4x6 and 3.5 x 5 color
      - Persuasions, The (musical group), 1972; 46288 (Box 8, Folder 43)
        One 8x10 color (mounted); one 5x7 b/w; two 3.5 x 5 color
      - Pike, Bishop James A. (Episcopal Bishop of California), 1968; 46287 (Box 8, Folder 44)
        One 5x7 and one 3.5 x 5 b/w
      - Pinney, A. Searle (opening A. Searl Pinney Hall/westside campus), 1999; 46286 (Box 8, Folder 45)
        One 4x5 color
      - Smithsonian (Michael Carrigan/James Roach signing partnership), 2003; 46285 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - Ratchford, William R. (Conn. State Rep., U.S. House of Rep.), ca.1960; 46284 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - Reynaldi, Nicholas (contemporary American poet), 1980; 46283 (Box 8, Folder 48)
        One 3.5 x 5 and one 5x7 b/w
      - Ribicoff, Abraham (Gov., Senator, House of Rep. from Conn.), ca.1960; 46282 (Box 8, Folder 49a)
      - Reich, Robert, Prof.of Public Policy at Berkeley, ca.1970; 46281 (Box 8, Folder 49b)
        One 5x7 and one 4x5 b/w
      - Roman, John III, St. Basil's Prep School, ca.1960; 46280 (Box 8, Folder 50)
      - Rukeyser, Louis (business columnist, economic commentator), 1988; 46279 (Box 8, Folder 51)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald H. and Robert Reich Debate, Ancell School of Business, ca.1980; 46278 (Box 8, Folder 52)
        Five 5x7; 19 3.5x5 color; one 4x5 b/w and contact sheets w/negatives
      - Sadow, Harvey S. (Chairman Boehringer Ingelheim) w/Stephen Feldman, ca.1980; 46277 (Box 8, Folder 53)
        Eight 5x7 b/w and contact sheets w/negatives
      - Serendipity Singers (musical group), 1964; 46276 (Box 8, Folder 54)
        One 8x10 b/w and one promotional flyer
      - Sheets, Dr. Robert, Dir. National Hurricane Center, 1990; 46275 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - Sibal, Abner W. (Congressman), ca.1960; 46274 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - Styron, William (author), 1990; 46273 (Box 8, Folder 57)
        Two 5x7 and one 5x5 b/w
      - Trifonov, Vlademir (Second Secy from the Soviet Embassy), 1967; 46272 (Box 8, Folder 58)
        One 5x6 and one 3.5 x 3.5 b/w
      - Union Gap (musical group), ca.1970; 46271 (Box 8, Folder 59)
        One 8x10, one 5x5, and one 5x7 b/w
      - Vito and the Salutations (musical group), ca.1970; 46270 (Box 8, Folder 60)
      - Wiegman, Clark (artist talk "Leaves of Knowledge), 2002; 46269 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Williford, Jack (pianist), includes Franciszek Zachara ca 1961, ca.1980; 46268 (Box 8, Folder 62)
        Four 3.5 x 4 b/w; three 3.5 x 5 color; one 8x10 b/w (Zachara)
      - Winston, Sherry (flutist), ca.1990; 46267 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      - Miscellaneous (unlabeled), ca.1960-1970; 46266 (Box 8, Folder 64)
        Six 5x7 and one 2.5x6 b/w
      - Wesport Players: History Broadcast? ("return to Danbury Teachers College"), 1949; 46265 (Box 8, Folder 64a)
      - Ancell School/Feldstein (Martin) & Gildner (George) Debate, ca. 1980; 50024 (Box 6.1, Folder 11)
        Three 4x6 b/w and 10 4x6 color
      - Wayne Baker, Connecticut State Senator, ca. 1980; 50025 (Box 6.1, Folder 12)
        One 3x3 square b/w
      - Caparn, Rhys, Artist, ca. 1969-1973; 50026 (Box 6.1, Folder 13)
      - Dodd, Senator Christopher, ca. 1980; 50027 (Box 6.1, Folder 14)
      - Dyer, James, ca. 1979; 50028 (Box 6.1, Folder 15)
        Four 5x7 b/w
      - Kissenger, Henry, 1987; 50029 (Box 6.1, Folder 16)
        16 8x10 b/w w/contact sheets
      - Ostar, Allan W., 50030 (Box 6.1, Folder 17)
      - Rosa, Anna Manicone, Pianist, ca. 1980; 50031 (Box 6.1, Folder 18)
      - Rumsfeld, Donald/Robert Reich Debate, ca. 1980; 50032 (Box 6.1, Folder 19)
        Four 5x7 b/w w/negatives, 19 3.5x5 color
      - Astronomy Speaker (unlabeled), 2001; 50148 (Box 6.3, Folder 1)
      - Brown, Jerry (former governor of California), 1997; 50149 (Box 6.3, Folder 2)
      - Clinton, President Bill, 2000; 50150 (Box 6.3, Folder 3)
        22 4x6 color
      - Clinton, President Bill (additional images), 2000; 50151 (Box 35)
        Approximately 500 color
      - Ghana Dance Ensemble, 2001; 50152 (Box 6.3, Folder 4)
      - Goodall, Jane (includes Dr. Roach and Denise Hogan), 1998; 50154 (Box 6.3, Folder 6)
      - Government Officials (Includes Barbara Kennerlly,Gov.Rowland,Chancellor Cibes and Board members, Mayor Eriquez, Pres.J.Roach), ca.1998; 50153 (Box 6.3, Folder 5)
        One 2.5x4 b/w; 11 4x5, one 3.5x5 and four 4x6 color
      - Rana, Swadesh, World Policy Institute, 1998; 50155 (Box 6.3, Folder 7)
      - Winston, Sherry (flutist), 2001; 50156 (Box 6.3, Folder 8)
      - Young, Robert (Includes Pres.Roach, Denise Hogan,A.Caraluzzi), 2000; 50157 (Box 6.3, Folder 9)
    - WCSU Centennial, 46262
      - Centennial cake cutting, 5K race, campus and students, 2003; 46263 (Box 8, Folder 65)
      - Fairfield Hall Tea; Pres.Roach and portrait by John Harris, artist and past WCSU grad; and Mirta Chakar w/baby Alexandra, 2002; 50331 (Box 5.4, Folder 2)
    - WestConn Society Community Award, 46259
      - Westconn 100 Luncheon/Groups, include Stephen Feldman, Irwin Kellner, Fred Leuthauser, Ed Goldberg, Per Eurell, Karl Epple, 1985; 50033 (Box 6.1, Folder 20)
      - Westconn 100 Luncheon/Groups, includes Stephen Feldman, Fred Leuthauser, Roy Young, 1986; 50034 (Box 6.1, Folder 21)
        Six 5x7 b/w/w contact sheets and negatives
      - Westconn 100 Luncheon/Groups, includes Stephen Feldman and unlabeled speaker, ca. 1990; 50035 (Box 6.1, Folder 22)
        Four 5x7, seven 3.5x5 b/w w/negatives
      - Westconn 100 Luncheon/Groups, includes Stephen Feldman and John Rich, 1991; 50036 (Box 6.1, Folder 23)
        Six 3.5x5 b/w w/negatives
      - Luncheon honoring Dr. John C. Rick, Pres. Of Hughes Danbury Optical Systems, 1991; 46261 (Box 8, Folder 66)
        Seven 3.5x5 b/w
      - Luncheon honoring Dr. James R. Roach, 2002; 46260 (Box 8, Folder 67)
        57 4x6 color
      - Luncheon, groups, candids/posed (Includes Mayor Eriquez,J.Roach,J.Goglietinno,B.Yamin,J.Ligi,I.Goldstein,C.Ociecki,D.Baskett,N.Whitfield,G.Lemme,J.Arconti,P.Palazzo,G.Robalotti,M.Driscoll,R.BensonR.Lewis,A.Krenick,Rep.Lew Wallace), 1998; 50143 (Box 6.2, Folder 28)
      - Luncheon, groups, candids/posed (Includes Chancellor Cibes,Mayor Eriquez, Dr.Roach, Denise Hogan, R.Gerber, A.Morton, F.Kathwari), 1999; 50144 (Box 6.2, Folder 29)
        Five 4x6 and five 3.5x5 color
      - Lucheon honoring Anthony and Roberta Caraluzzi, posed (Includes Pres.Roach,A.Morton,G.Buccini,M.Damyan,M.Driscoll,S.Caraluzzi,R.Caraluzzi, ca.2000; 50145 (Box 6.2, Folder 31)
        50 4x6 color
      - Luncheon honoring Danbury Mayor Gene Eriquez, posed and candids (partially labeled), 2001; 50146 (Box 6.2, Folder 31)
      - Luncheon, groups, candids/posed, published in WestConn Pillars 2002-2003 (Includes G.Hawley,H.Wibling,I.Farington,J.Luncy,T.Eberhard,T.Crucitti,N.Wagner,Mayor Boughton), 50147 (Box 6.2, Folder 32)
    - Western Connecticut State University Awards Ceremonies, 46257
      - Unidentified students, ca.1960-1970; 46258 (Box 8, Folder 68)
        Three 8x10, five 5x7, one 4 x 7.5, one 4x5, four 3.5 x 3.5 b/w
    - Negatives/Contact Sheets, 46241
      - President Clinton's visit, September 11, 2000, ca 1970-2000, 46256 (Box 24, Folder 6)
        35mm color negatives
      - Commencement, 1980; 46255 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Commencement, ca.1980-1990; 46254 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Commencement, 1982; 46253 (Box 24, Folder 9)
        Contact sheet w/negatives
      - Commencement, ca.1990; 46252 (Box OS 6)
        Contact sheets
      - Commencement, 1976-1981; 46251 (Box 24, Folder 10)
      - Convocation, 1983; 46250 (Box 24, Folder 11)
      - Governor's Luncheon, 1979; 46249 (Box 24, Folder 12)
      - Minority Education (cover); A Report of a Danbury Regional Symposium, WCSU, April 1987, 46248 (Box 24, Folder 13)
      - Open House, Ruth Haas Library 10/18/1970, 46247 (Box 24, Folder 14)
      - Rhys Caparn, Library sculpture reception, 1969-1973; 46246 (Box 24, Folder 15)
      - SGA/Haas retirement citation, 1975; 46245 (Box 24, Folder 16)
      - University Ball, ca.1980; 46244 (Box 24, Folder 17)
        One contact sheet w/negatives
      - Unknown (Gov.O'Neill, Dr. Feldman, Dr. Lu, Roy Young, Nathan Ancell), ca.1980; 46243 (Box 24, Folder 18)
        Four contact sheets and 35mm b/w negatives
      - Unknown/Westside (includes Nathan Ancell, Harvey Sadow, Gov. O'Neill, Stephen Feldman, Robert Bersi, Frank Muska, et al), ca.1980; 46242 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Faculty/Staff, 45642
    - Faculty, 45657
      - Alberetti, Robert D., Art w/students (ca.1930 - ca.1990), ca.1980-1990; 45720 (Box 20, Folder 1)
        7 5x7 b/w
      - Bannister, Jerry, Social Science (portrait), ca.1990; 45719 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Boelke, Walter, Prof. Art (candid), ca.1990; 45718 (Box 20, Folder 3)
        5x7 and three 3.5x5 b/w
      - Butterworth, Thomas M., Biology (portrait and classroom), ca.1990; 45717 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Chance, Alice, Chemistry (portrait), ca.1990; 45716 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Chen, Chin, Prof. Oceanography (portrait), ca.1980; 45715 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Dahill, Jr., Edwin M., Social Science (portrait), ca.1960; 45714 (Box 20, Folder 7)
        One 2x4 b/w
      - Dow, Janet, English (portrait), ca.1990; 45713 (Box 20, Folder 8)
        One 3.5x5 b/w
      - Dye, Frank, Biology (portrait), ca.1990; 45712 (Box 20, Folder 9)
        One 8x10 b/w, and one 2x3 color
      - Echevarria, Abraham, Art, ca.1990; 45711 (Box 20, Folder 10)
        Three 5x7 and two 3.5x5 b/w
      - Fryer, Russell G., Political Science & History (portrait and with SGA President), ca.1960-1990; 45710 (Box 20, Folder 11)
        One 8x10 and one 5x7 b/w
      - Geyer, Joseph, Music, 1965; 45709 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Goldstein, Melvin, Meteorology (with Ella Grasso, Ruth Haas, family and portrait), ca.1970-1990; 45708 (Box 20, Folder 13)
        One 8x10 and five 5x7 b/w and contact sheets w/negatives
      - Grimes, Margaret, Art (portrait, candids, and award), ca.1980-1990; 45707 (Box 20, Folder 14)
        Six 5x7 and one 3.5x5 b/w
      - Halliburton, Richard, Biology (portrait), ca.1990; 45706 (Box 20, Folder 15)
      - Hamer, Josephine, Mathematics (portrait), ca.1990; 45705 (Box 20, Folder 16)
      - Hart, Richie, Music (Jazz), ca.1970; 45704 (Box 20, Folder 17)
        Two 3.5x5 b/w
      - Hines, Paul S., Chemistry, ca.1970-1990; 45703 (Box 20, Folder 18)
        Three 5x7 and one 3x5 b/w, one 2x3 color
      - Hobbs, Howard, Social Science (candid), ca.1970; 45702 (Box 20, Folder 19)
      - Isaacs, Kevin, Music (portrait and candid), ca.1990; 45701 (Box 20, Folder 20)
        One 4x5 and one 3.5x5 b/w
      - Jalbert, Norine L., Psychology (portrait), ca.1990; 45700 (Box 20, Folder 21)